http://www.apex-books.com/apex/company/privacy_policy.htm

Privacy Policy
THE INFORMATION ABOUT YOU COLLECTED ON THIS WEB SITE IS SUBJECT TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY. BY DISCLOSING THE INFORMATION TO US, YOU AGREE TO THE TERMS OF THE POLICY. Apex Publishers recognizes the importance of protecting the privacy of our customers and visitors to our Web site while permitting us to conduct legitimate business by providing services and information of interest to our customers and visitors. Our privacy policy is stated below.
Collection of Information
We will collect certain personal information when you register for our services or purchase our products. During registration we will ask you to set up a user name and password to establish secure access to your personal information. We will also ask you for your name, address, phone number, and email address. This contact information that you provide at registration allows you to:
buy items without having to re-enter your personal information every time you purchase a product
view all your purchases and shipments from the On line Book Store 24 hours a day, seven days a week
When you purchase a product, we ask you for your name, billing address, shipping address (if different from billing address), phone number, email address, and payment information. The payment and contact information is used to complete and verify the transaction, and your email address allows us to contact you regarding the receipt, completion, and shipping of your transaction and product. We maintain this information in our secure customer database. We may use "cookies" to recognize you and your access privileges on our site, as well as to trace site usage. A cookie is a piece of information that is sent to your Web browser from a Web site and stored on your computer's hard drive. Each time you return to our site, we are able to identify you as a previous or registered customer. Cookies also enable us to measure our site traffic, including the number of repeat versus new visitors, the time users spend online, and their navigation behavior. Collecting this information allows us to make changes that improve our site.
Use of Information
The information that we collect is used to provide the service or product requested; to enable billing and shipping; to provide you with information about related products and services; to improve our Web site, for development of new products and services; and for systems administration and troubleshooting purposes. Except where necessary in connection with services provided by appropriate intermediaries, who will be required to comply with the confidentiality provisions of this policy, Apex Publishers will not disclose any personal information identifying Users to any third party, unless required by law or otherwise needed in connection with legal proceedings or unless we have received your consent.
Your Rights
Requests for the correction of personal information or removal of information should be directed to Apex Publishers by contacting us. In addition, please understand that information about you in our databases may come from a number of sources, including orders placed by you and third-party mailing lists.
Privacy Contact: Questions regarding this policy should be directed to Apex Publishers. Apex is not responsible for the privacy policies of Web sites to which this site may link.
When you purchase books from Apex Publishers, you have several shipping options, and should be aware of our shipping practices.
Home
About Us
Privacy Policy
Terms of Use Agreement
Contact Us
© Copyright 2019 Apex Publishers or related companies. All rights reserved.
No part of this content or the data or information included therein may be reproduced, republished or redistributed without the prior written consent of Apex Publishers. Use of this site is governed by our Copyright Policy, Terms of Use Agreement and Privacy Policy.
